DENYS SAMOILENKO

FRONT

CONTACT INFO

(+380)99-079-85-17 (<u>Telegram</u>)

<u>M denys.samoilenko.dev@gmail.com</u>

in LinkedIn

(C) GitHub

Kremenchuk / Remote

with After experimenting various programming languages, I made the decision to specialize Front-end in development. I appreciate the abundant job prospects and the vast array of libraries and frameworks available within this field. It's akin to becoming a versatile expert in the realm of web technology. I am highly organized, punctual, and a responsible individual. Additionally, I have achieved victory in various futsal and football tournaments.

SKILLS

Programming Languages and Frameworks:

- TypeScript; JavaScript, jQuery
- React, Redux Toolkit, Next.js,
- Vue.js

Front-End Development:

- HTML5, CSS3, Sass (SCSS), BEM
- Bootstrap, Tailwind

Back-End Development:

- Fetch, REST API, SQL
- Node.js, Express

Design and Prototyping:

- Figma, Zeplin

Development Tools:

- Git/Github: Visual Studio Code
- Chrome Developer Tools (including React)
- NPM

Methodologies and Project Management:

- Agile, Scrum, ClickUp, Trello

Algorithmic Problem Solving:

- 200+ solved algorithmic tasks

Other Skills:

- Contentful, TanStack

PROJECTS

My Portfolio (Next.js + Contentful)

Demo

Code

EXPERIENCE

february 2024 - september 2024 **Front End Developer**

- Working with HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS, TS, React, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind, REST API.
- · Created animated responsive sites using jQuery and React + typescript for real estate agencies and service industries. Worked on the creation of a CRM system.
- I created sites thanks to which I managed to attract more people and the flow of clients in the real estate sector as realtors and buying/selling.
- Since I was one frontend developer, I managed to significantly improve how to solve problems and understand new libraries on my own.

july 2023 - february 2024 Front End Developer

- · Working with HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS, TS, React, Next, NodeJS, Express.
- Carrying out more than 170 development tasks such as websites, functions, and web applications on React using RESTful API and with Backend, NodeJS with Express, and DB on SQL.
- · I have theoretical knowledge in the field of Manual QA, and experience in compiling bug reports.

Sales manager

"Anteks"

2015 - 2023

- I expanded our reach to people in another region of Ukraine.
- It is now available in numerous supermarkets and stores, resulting in a sales increase from the initial 300,000 to 1 million per month

EDUCATION HISTORY

Specialist Degree of metrology and measurement technology

2009 - 2015

National Technical University -«Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute»

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

Full - stack course at Mate academy Manual QA course at Ukrainian It School Codeacademy(HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React)